export const topick6 = [
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the oldest lighthouse in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'White Lighthouse',
      b: 'Light Tower',
      c: 'Sea Tower',
    },
    answer: 'Light Tower',
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year was the first lighthouse of Ostend built?',
    options: {
      a: '1584',
      b: '1721',
      c: '1830',
    },
    answer: '1721',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What structure was built to protect the port of Ostend in the 18th century?',
    options: {
      a: "Napoleon's Fortress",
      b: "Lion's Gate",
      c: 'Dragon Tower',
    },
    answer: "Napoleon's Fortress",
  },
  {
    question:
      'What important architectural building was completed in Ostend in 1905?',
    options: {
      a: 'Fish market',
      b: 'Maritime exchange',
      c: 'Grand Hotel',
    },
    answer: 'Grand Hotel',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What building is the main symbol of the maritime history of Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Maritime Museum',
      b: 'Grand Hotel',
      c: 'White Lighthouse',
    },
    answer: 'Maritime Museum',
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year was the Maritime Exchange of Ostend built?',
    options: {
      a: '1601',
      b: '1701',
      c: '1801',
    },
    answer: '1801',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What architectural style predominates in the buildings of the port of Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Gothic',
      b: 'Baroque',
      c: 'Neoclassical',
    },
    answer: 'Neoclassical',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which tower in Ostend was built in honor of the victory over the pirates?',
    options: {
      a: "Sailor's Tower",
      b: 'Victory Tower',
      c: 'Defense Tower',
    },
    answer: 'Victory Tower',
  },
  {
    question: 'What building was constructed in Ostend in 1838?',
    options: {
      a: 'Maritime Museum',
      b: 'Railway Station',
      c: "Napoleon's Fortress",
    },
    answer: 'Railway Station',
  },
  {
    question: 'What structure was built to improve shipping in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Light Tower',
      b: 'Sea Canal',
      c: 'Fish Market',
    },
    answer: 'Sea Canal',
  },
];
